allgive.com 2010-11-16

# Allgive.com Privacy Policy

This statement discloses the privacy practices for Allgive.com, a Litmus Media, Inc. holding. Our goal is to provide quality web search results while distributing a portion of all proceeds generated to the charities our users chose to support. 

What Personally Identifiable Information of yours is collected: When you visit Allgive.com, you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself (e.g., contact and demographic information). We use this information to respond to your inquiries and to customize your search experience on Allgive.com. 

When you perform a web search or click on a search result link, we utilize patent-pending ValidClick technology to monitor your search and click activity and to collect data required to validate your search and click traffic to prevent fraud and assure our advertisers.  Such data will include your computer's IP address, mouse movements, search volume, click volume, terms searched, and which listings were clicked on.

COOKIES

To enable many of the features available at Allgive.com, we may assign "cookies" to your Internet browser. A cookie is a small text file that contains a unique identification number stored on your computer. Cookies by themselves cannot be used to find out the identity of any user. This unique identification number automatically identifies your browser - but not you - to our computers whenever you interact with Allgive.com. These cookies will allow us to credit the proper charity for the searches you perform on Allgive.com. These cookies are also set so we may better customize your experience on Allgive.com for your future visits. You are free to reject or "Not Accept" the placement of some or all of our cookies.

When you visit Allgive.com, you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself (e.g., contact and demographic information). We use this information to respond to your inquiries and to customize your search experience on Allgive.com. 

When you perform a web search or click on a search result link, we utilize patent-pending ValidClick technology to monitor your search and click activity and to collect data required to validate your search and click traffic to prevent fraud and assure our advertisers.  Such data will include your computer's IP address, mouse movements, search volume, click volume, terms searched, and which listings were clicked on. 

There is a lot of confusion about cookies, how they are used, and what they can do. Cookies only contain information that the server computer "knew" in the first place, and can only be read by the serving domain that placed them. For instance, if XYZ.com (a fictitious company) utilizes cookies, Allgive’s servers can't read their contents nor can XYZ.com's servers read ours. Cookies are an essential part of how the Internet works today, and allow server computers to recognize your computer's browser when you return. If you have ever visited a Web page that automatically provides personalized content without you having to "sign in," such as your own stock portfolio, this is almost certainly being accomplished with a cookie. Since cookies are only text files, they cannot "run" on your computer and have no ability to search your computer for other information, or transmit it to anyone. 

What Organization is collecting the information: 

The data you provide to Allgive.com is collected by Litmus Media, Inc. 

How the information is used: 

The personal profile information you submit to Allgive.com remains your property, but by submitting that information you grant Litmus Media the right to use that information for marketing purposes. 

How the information is shared: 

We DO NOT share, rent or sell the personal information that you supply to us.  We may join together with other businesses to bring selected targeted opportunities to you based on information you submitted. In addition, Litmus Media reserves the right to release information collected (1) in the event Litmus Media believes such information pertains to an unlawful act, (2) if the information is subpoenaed, (3) if Litmus Media is sold or acquired, (4) or when Litmus Media deems it necessary or appropriate. 

Litmus Media operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary, and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our members. 

Third-Party Links 

We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other Web sites. We encourage you to note when you click through to a third party website from Allgive.com, you should read the privacy statements of such Web sites. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Litmus Media, Inc. on Allgive.com. 

Children 

You must be at least 13 years of age to submit information to Litmus Media. If you are under 13, you will not be allowed to submit information to Litmus Media. Litmus Media has implemented this policy and technology to comply with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). 

Contacting Litmus Media, Inc. 

Litmus Media respects your privacy and uses the information you provide us with integrity and full disclosure. If you ever feel this policy has been broken, let us know. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of Litmus Media, or your dealings with us, please contact us by email to Privacy@ Litmus Media.com or by postal mail to: Litmus Media, Inc., 310 Armour Rd, Suite 203, North Kansas City, MO 64116, Attn: Privacy Dept.
